Stand up.
We defeated you.
A dozen Alps just became martyrs.
You all died, Alps.
Why didn't you check the Alps lost behind you?
Why didn't you inform your brothers?
If you had been careful, even if
four brothers became martyrs...
...you should have exposed the
ambush. But you didn't care and kept going.
You ran away.
But I will teach all of you.
All of you.
Either the easy way..
...or the hard way.
Now..
...I expect all of you in my tent tonight.
You are in trouble, Alps.
Turgut Ghazi will make you pay for this.
Let's go to the tent, come on.
Thinner, sister, thinner.
Praise be.
Ghazi!
May the flood take you, Ghazi!
Help me stay patient, God.
Ulgen.
What happened to you?
Don't even ask, my Bala.
I cannot think clearly.
This Ghazi, may he suffer.
While chasing him to
catch him, I fell down the hill.
Let me see
Get well soon. Come, come, sit and rest.
I can't rest. Who will cook the food?
Come, sit and rest. Or you'll faint.
You'll faint. Hold her.
Careful.
Mother!
Mother..
My daughter.
What happened?
Mother, among the sisters,
no one fights better than me.
But my sister didn't let
me rest even for a minute.
You are right about your fighting skills.
But you must keep
training until you fight like us.
Stop training now.
I will give you a duty.
Mother... What duty is it?
You will cook dinner tonight.
You will prepare your father's table.
Us?
But mother, I'm still learning.
Mother..
Are you sure?
Or else we might starve.
Aunt..
Why would you say that?
No my Fatma, I'm joking.
But I'll help them, mother.
No, no.
Only the two of them will do it. You can do it.
Are they going to compete?
Whose food is better, Bala Hatun?
Don't grow the fire!
I can't even get up. They are already nervous!
Ulgen. Calm down.
Ghazi..
You can do it, girls, you can. Go now.
We can. We can, mother but where is my father?
Let's ask him what he wants to eat.
Your father is not in the tribe, my daughter.
He'll see you when he comes in the evening.
Mother, where is my father?
I don't know, my daughter.
Come on.
I will make the best food for my father.
Don't even run. We'll start at the same time.
Halime, I told you to stop.
O passenger! Where are you going?
To The Red Apple.
What is your goal?
Shahada.
What do you want to reunite with?
With the state.
Where is the state?
The whole world.
O, the one waiting.
For the sake of armies whose horses spark
fire and whose swords bring justice, tell me.
Where is the Red Apple?
-Peace be upon you.
-Peace be upon you too.
Have a seat, Osman Bey.
Thank you.
Osman Bey, son of Ertugrul Ghazi.
You didn't disappoint
You brought Mongolians to kneel.
You devastated Byzantine.
You became victorious in both fronts.
Thank you, thank you.
We didn't get victorious thanks
to our strength but our faith.
I'm trying to spread Islam, the right religion.
And I will never give up.
Surely, Osman Bey.
We heard, saw and confirmed.
But you should know that there
are harder times ahead of you.
You fate is between a scorpion's clamps.
The enemy got defeated but...
...they are gaining power again.
They'll attack you with all their strength.
It won't be a war of welfare.
But it's a war of existence.
I'm trying to make the state prevail forever.
We are never afraid of death.
I don't care if they all attack.
But you are getting weaker
in this fight day by day.
Your struggle has caused great wounds in you.
The number of your alps has decreased.
I know. I know.
You say you know, Osman Bey.
So tell us about the measures you will take.
Alps who cannot use swords are chained.
Alps without a family
jeopardize the future of the state.
For this reason,
...I will make all the single alps get married.
I'll build a commission about that.
I will use every means available.
And the children to be born
will flourish our state forever.
Thank you, Osman bey.
As the number of heathens increases,
...you have do that to be equal to them.
The state is the one that
always foresees the future.
Being minority means annihilation for a nation.
New generations mean hope.
Otherwise
...there will be no liberty in these lands.
We will help you with this.
Turkmen tribes have already left from Iraq
and Aleppo to increase your population.
You will help them settle.
Alps will come to use swords
and merchants to make trade.
In this way, the taxes you
get with both battle and trade...
..will improve your state.
Tax is the most important system
that improves a state, Osman Bey.
It's the insurance of the future.
Of course... Of course, you're right.
We always have place for Turkmen.
They are welcome here.
It'll be better for me if I know when they come.
They will be here in fifteen dawns.
Make them settle in the lands that
you will conquer next, Osman Bey.
Okay.
We herald conquests for you.
May swords be drawn.
May the banner of justice raise in the sky.
Sure.
When the Seljuk State collapsed
...Beys without a head
turned against each other.
While Turks needed to stand united,
...each of them wanted to be the leader.
And they worked for their own.
Of course.
But you, Osman Bey, chose
the Islam cause for Turks.
-You fought the heathens on your own.
-Sure I did.
For this reason
...light the fire of conquest.
It is such a huge fire...
...it will be an ember for the
tyrants and hope for the oppressed.
God willing.
Horses of Turks will reach the
frontiers like the head of a mare!
March, Osman Bey.
You march so the blind dagger
of betrayal will get broken...
...and the justice of Islam will
spread all around the world.
The fire of heathens will go out.
Heathens will be destroyed.
I swear..
...the lands of Turks will flourish.
Either a leader rules...
..or ravens chew dead bodies.
May you live long.
I brought greetings from
Osman Bey, Bey of Beys,
who brought order and
justice in the frontiers.
-Peace be upon you too.
Osman Bey is having a council tomorrow.
He desires to see you and all
the other Beys in the council.
We appreciate the regards and
invitation of the heir of Oghuz kin.
But why is Osman Bey having a council?
Do you have any information, Aykurt Cavus.
I don't know, Koca Bey.
My Bey just ordered us to invite the Beys.
As Osman Bey orders.
Okay.
Osman Bey is expecting all his Beys tomorrow.
He'II hold a council.
He orders you to join, Hasan Bey.
Osman Bey, the conquer.
He's invited all the beys.
It must be an important matter, huh, Kanyumaz?
Kanyumaz doesn't know, Hasan Bey.
I just deliver the message.
When the council starts
tomorrow everyone will know.
Alright, Kanyumaz.
Osman Bey's wish is a command to me.
Sure, my Bey.
Why do you think he's having
a council so suddenly, brother?
We will see when we go.
Did you really not know he would have a council?
Would I have asked if I had known?
As he is gathering all the
beys, it must be an urgent matter.
Obviously, Osman Bey is about
to make an important decision.
And that means...
Excuse me, brother.
I need to make preparations for tomorrow.
Stop.
Seyit.
Go inform Claudius.
I have important things to tell him.
Here we go.
I make beef roasting.
And she makes bulghur.
Her job is easier. It's not fair.
Oh come on. Fatma
Halime is just learning this stuff.
Even this job is too hard for her.
No, it's not hard.
I'm a quick learner.
Oh really?
I'm supposed to add water, right?
How much water should I add?
Well...
I've just taught you.
I'm not saying anything because
Bala Hatun told me to be easy on her.
Look at the bottle she took!
Halime, my dear!
Halime, my dear...
Only that much water for that bulghur?
You know? Do you get it?
You don't get it.
Do you think it's enough?
Halime, Halime.
That water isn't enough.
You need to pour until the water gets above.
Well...
My beef roasting will be
overcooked because of you!
Sister.
You don't want to upset me, right?
I just don't want to upset my mother and father.
Not to make them starve.
If I don't help you, we will die of hunger.
Halime, oil!
Oil, Halime!
Oil.
-Oh I forgot. Oil.
-Yes.
I'm supposed to add salt, right?
Yes, Halime.
Hurry, hurry.
Hurry, Halime!
Mine is about to be overcooked.
My kitchen has turned into a battlefield!
Give me that roller, sister.
Thanks. Ghazi!
You naughty boy, Ghazi!
You put this competition thing in their minds!
Competition is good, mother.
Our stomachs will be filled.
Right?
Like your stomach has never been filled!
Like father like son.
I was so hungry, Ghazi. Well thought.
Don't worry.
I will teach you how to do it.
Don't be worrying, brother.
Mother.
Come, my girl.
They are not cooking but fighting.
Give it to me, Halime!
My Allah!
Give me.
-Mother.
-Yes?
Do you know why my father
is having a council tomorrow?
Everybody is wondering.
I don't know, my dear.
But Osman Bey has been thoughtful for days.
After the council, all of
us will know, God willing.
God willing.
Allah is Eternal!
Allah is The Righteous!
-Allah is Eternal!
-Allah is The Righteous!
Peace be upon you.
-Peace be upon you too.
-Peace be upon you too, sergeant Aykurt.
What are you doing here?
-We are forging.
Praise be. Praise be.
These brave alps are the sons
of a bey who we appreciate.
-Praise be.
-They're very interested in horses.
Well... I called you so they
could learn from the best.
Hay Praise be.
So, you are interested in the friend
and companion of Turks, the horses, huh?
Then follow me and I will
teach you everything I know.
Come on.
Come with me.
Hay Praise be.
They say Allah created humans
from soil and horses from the wind.
Can an Alp be without a companion? No.
Does Osman Bey have a companion?
You are looking right at it.
The other horses neigh.
Why doesn't this horse neigh?
It looks quiet but speaks with
its heart. Look into its eyes.
It knows a lot, it doesn't say a thing.
It travels far, but it does not complain.
If you talk to it, it listens to you.
How will we talk to it?
Tell me, what is your name?
MelikShah Alp.
Praise be MelikShah.
Well-said.
We read the soul of the horse.
We look into its eyes.
Are its ears upright? Is its tail calm?
If you know how to look, it gives you answers.
Then we speak with them.
Watch carefully, MelikShah, learn.
Now this horse came from the
road and is tired. We will groom it.
What happens if we don't groom it?
Good question, Alparslan Alp.
If we don't groom it, the horse's
fur gets tangled. Its skin itches.
It won't even walk.
And if the saddle hurts its
back, it won't listen to you.
It won't even look at you.
Now..
Now we start from the neck.
Then the back.
Then here.
Most importantly, these thin legs.
We also groom the legs.
If you approach it from behind,
it will kick you in the chest.
The companion of the valiants,
the noble brother of the Alp.
Sometimes it is his secret keeper,
never returns from battle without him.
We go on the road of war,
and we swear with our hearts.
It bows its head and listens to your
words if you don't pull the reins too hard.
Its hooves break stones,
its mane falls over its face.
If you care for it well, it shines like a star.
The crescent moon appears in its noble eyes.
You prepared a welcome suitable
for a Byzantine nobleman, Claudius.
I have always been kind to my friends.
Especially to those who bring me information.
Sit down.
You and I share the same fate.
I am a sharp sword...
...you are a long spear.
We are now on the same path.
I believe that.
Now tell me what you know, Yigit Bey.
Osman Bey will hold a council.
He invited all the Beys.
As you know...
..when Osman Bey calls for a council...
...a storm follows it.
You need to learn what
decisions are made in that council.
I will learn.
Once we start working together...
...we will defeat Osman together.
But in return..
...you will
give me gold and the land of Goynuk.
And I will settle my tribe there.
"My" tribe?
I guess you mean your brother's tribe.
Or you will bring your brother down.
Good.
Do we have a deal, Claudius?
We do.
You will get everything you
want when Osman's rule is over.
God willing.
Here.
Your burden must be heavy, right, my Osman?
Is it the burden of the tomorrow's council?
My burden is heavy. It is.
I have a long way to go, Bala.
Whenever I come to you, whenever I come here...
...I forget about my burden.
I always feel better here.
I wish I could help you more.
Look, today another one of our
dreams will come true. Dark Osman.
What is it?
Our daughters have been in the
kitchen since morning, cooking for you.
Really? They are cooking for me?
Who else would it be? They are
preparing a table for their father.
They are competing with each other
too. We dreamed of this so much.
Right, Bala.
All the things we thought impossible
are coming true one by one.
You used to tell me,
"Servants plan, but fate laughs."
Right? Do you remember?
Right.
I said that.
If only you could see, Osman.
When I saw them happy and
together, I thanked my Allah.
Our dreams are coming true.
You once opposed me.
You wanted to leave me
because of a wound, remember?
I told you, we would have a daughter, we would
have children, and our family would grow.
You see?
Now they are cooking for
Thanks to Allah.
Fortunately, my Osman.
Yes, fortunately.
Alps, now all of you will
pull yourselves together.
Alps.
Let me tell you this.
Turgut Ghazi will break your bones.
You won't even be able to sleep.
He will make you train day and night.
Peace be upon you
Peace be upon you too
Come, Turgut Ghazi.
Thank you.
Sit, Alps.
Alps...
Today, what brought
you defeat during the drill...
...was the weakness of your brotherhood bond.
There are brothers who put others in trouble.
And there are brothers who bring victories.
Now..
...I will tell you the story of...
...two brave brothers who
always fought together.
One time..
...I heard it from the late Suleyman Shah.
This story has almost
everything, nothing is left out.
It has all the truth, there
is not a single lie in it.
It is called a story...
...but it is real.
During their time...
..there were two brothers...
...who founded the Seljuk State, which
was the strongest and biggest state...
..in the world.
One of them was the master of
politics, the Sultan of Sultans...
...Tugrul Bey...
The other was his older brother,
the commander of commanders...
...the master of battlefields...
...the one who could break
swords with bare hands...
...Cagri Bey.
At that time, the land was watered with blood.
As the earth shook...
...the blue sky turned the color of blood.
While every nation
fought for its own survival...
...the foundation and
rise of the Seljuk State...
...were tied to the lives of these two brothers.
After their father passed
away, Cagri Bey made a
decision that was very rare
and shocked everyone deeply.
What decision did he make, Turgut Ghazi?
Even though the throne
rightfully belonged to Cagri
Bey, he gave it to his
younger brother Tugrul Bey.
How did he defeat his nafs, Turgut Ghazi?
How did he not want to be the ruler?
Cagri Bey was a leader
who was always victorious.
He was the master of battlefields.
No one could stand against his
sword. No one could stand against him.
Tugrul Bey was a skilled ruler...
...a brave Sultan who was a master of politics.
They never wanted something for themselves.
Tugrul Bey's wisdom and Cagri Bey's
sword gained victories one after another.
They rode across continents.
When war started and the storm came...
...when they shot the Seljuk arrows to the sky..
...they could even block out the sun.
The dark ground would get even darker.
The warriors from Turkistan,
riding fast horses like eagles...
...ripped the hearts of their enemies!
Hay Praise be.
These two brothers, these two noble Beys...
...chose to be united and strong
instead of fighting each other.
They always chose to cover each other's flaws.
One became the mind of the
state, the other the sword of justice.
Everyone in the world heard about them. They
walked together for the cause of Islam...
...and built a great state.
They never gave up their roots
or the legacy of their ancestors.
While Sultan Tugrul built a
civilization in the capital city of Rey...
...Cagri Bey stayed in Khorasan
and trained the army in his tribe.
These two selfless men
established that great state this way.
Praise be.
What you should learn from this story is...
...always be united and stay strong.
War is not only won on the battlefield.
True victory comes from
brave hearts that beat together...
...that never ask for...
...something for itselves.
Yes, Turgut Ghazi.
Alaeddin, Gonca.
My Bey.
Where are your sisters?
Don't even ask, father.
They'll come now
I swear I did nothing wrong, my Bey.
Alright then, let's sit.
In the name of Allah,
the merciful, the compassionate.
I told you. We're late.
Our father is waiting for us.
It's not my fault.
It was you who kept interrupting me, sister.
Father, look. I made bulghur for you.
Yes, raw bulghur.
Taste my roasting.
It's perfectly cooked.
We will see.
Bala, you see? Our daughters cook for us now.
Yes.
Praise be to my girls.
Let's eat.
Let's eat and make a choice.
You leave it. Ulgen, let's do it together.
Wait, wait.
You sit beside me. Come on.
Well, we'll eat together.
We'll eat together.
You see, hatun?
We have got forgotten already.
Just wait, Alaaddin. Don't be jealous.
He's implying Fatma, my dear.
Don't mess with my girls. Alaaddin Bey.
Well, mother... You already call me Bey?
Don't mess with my daughters.
Here we go. In the name of Allah,
the merciful, the compassionate.
Let's start with this.
Alaaddin.
How do you like, father? Is it well cooked?
Very good.
The meat is nicely cooked,
sister. Thanks for cooking.
Of course it is, brother.
Because I made the roasting.
If you want to see Halime's
skills, taste the bulghur.
Hey, you've already started
teaching your sister? Good girl.
Well..
Train her to fight. Teach her to cook.
-And?
-Make her memorize the Quran surahs.
And
Do I have to deal with you?
Whatever.
There is nothing to do.
I have to teach, I guess.
-You have to.
-I have to teach.
The bulghur is uncooked.
And the meat is too hard.
Why didn't you tell us?
No, my dear. It's the best
meal I have ever tasted.
Right?
Yes, yes. Very nice.
Come closer to me.
What matters is you cooked them.
Besides, you will know better by practicing.
Ulgen.
My daughter will cook the
meals of the tribe from now on.
Oh no, my Bey.
My kitchen has turned into a battlefield.
What?
-Sister Ulgen!
-I mean it.
Halime, I told you to add
water. Didn't you do it?
My roasting got overcooked
because I was trying to help you.
Well, my Bey...
Who do you think won?
Well... Well..
Sisterhood won today.
But I don't know what
happens next time. Alright?
-Fine.
-Here we go.
-Let's eat.
-Alaaddin, eat.
I will eat, my Bey.
Thank you, hatun.
I'm starving. I'm starving.
Where is your mother, Ghazi?
Where are the meals Ghazi? I'm starving!
Father, have you ever been full?
Don't hit him.
The boy will be stupid!
A spoon can't make him stupid.
They hit harder woods on my head.
I see... That's why you are like this.
I thought Allah created you like that.
Give it to me.
Come on, come on.
What did you mean by saying that?
I didn't mean to say anything, Cerkutay.
Don't mess with me. I feel terrible.
-In the name of Allah.
Ulgen.
Do we live in a desert, Ulgen?
Is there no water in the wells?
Did all the bottles get broken?
This isn't a meal but rock!
This needs to be boiled. It's like
rock! My teeth almost got broken!
Father, it wasn't my mother who...
What do you mean by saying that, Cerkutay?
Don't you like the meal I cooked?
-I like it.
-Yes.
I like it. How can I not like the meal you cook?
Good. You eat all of it then.
Here. Take it. Come on, eat.
Enjoy your meal.
Pour water, Ghazi.
Pour some water.
Well... Great meals for my Bey!
I can't swallow.
Sufficient for us is Allah, and
He is the best Disposer of affairs.
Help. Help. Help me, my Allah.
Help, help, help.
Help.
I seek refuge in Allah
from the outcast Shaitan. In
the name of Allah, The
Compassionate, The Merciful.
Help me, my Allah.
Turgut Ghazi.
No. Sit.
What? Couldn't you sleep either?
When there is moonlight.
...I can't sleep, Osman.
Tell me. Why didn't you sleep?
I had such a nightmare...
I was trapped inside the walls.
My hands and feet were chained.
I tried to get out of there.
Did you get out?
-No.
I couldn't.
I started hitting.
I tried to break them.
I felt some fire when I broke.
Such a fire..
May Allah make it herald the good.
What burns you?
The fire or the burden of
the state on your shoulders?
My father once told me.
"When you become a Bey
...you will understand me."
This burden of the state...
This shirt of fire.
To reach our goals
..I have to pay too much.
This axe..
You know how this axe is made, right?
By forging.
It becomes like this by getting hits.
Blows one after another inside the flames.
It gets cool in the water.
But then it burns again.
How could it be so hard and strong...
..if it didn't suffer so much?
And you?
If you hadn't suffered all those things.
If you hadn't burned in flames,
what would have happened?
I don't care about my own suffering.
I'm thinking about the decision I
need to make in the council tomorrow.
I care about my people.
Well..
We need conquests.
But my people are just regaining strength.
That's why I'm thinking of my people.
Suffering and reward.
Blessing and trouble.
They only come from Allah.
You need to move forward, Osman.
You made many enemies kneel until this day.
Of course, many more enemies
will set traps against you on this path.
As they set traps...
...you and your descendants will
make history with Allah's permission.
God willing.
God willing. God willing.
This is...
...a test for all of us, Osman.
All of us.
Those who pass the test...
...will reach the target.
Come on now.
Get up now.
Your heart...
...is as big as the state.
Do what your heart tells you to do.
As long as my Allah...
..allows me..
...I will never give up on this path.
Praise be to you.
We will reignite the Byzantine
fire on the frontiers, Sofia.
We will root Turks out from the frontiers.
First, Osman.
My alliance with Osman...
...did not give me anything.
I even lost what I had in
my hands, Great Emperor.
I am at your service.
What is your order for me?
First...
I order you to leave the past behind, Sofia.
This dastard...
...must be locked in a dungeon, Great Emperor.
You were the one who betrayed, Sofia.
If I am here..
...it's because I am loyal to our Emperor.
Enough!
As we fight with each other...
...Osman gets even stronger!
For the Great Roman Empire
...you will end the enmity between you.
He stole Bursa from me.
Great Emperor.
And you stole my trust in you, Sofia.
But to see Osman suffering in pain...
...I can do anything.
Including giving the throne of Bursa...
..to Sofia.
You will rule Bursa together.
Then we will destroy Osman...
I will also divide his properties
we seize between you two.
As you order.
It is the best time to unite.
Tomorrow, Osman will hold a
council with his Beys tomorrow.
If he is gathering his all Beys...
...he must be after something big.
And it will surely affect Byzantium.
We will find out what will be
talked about there. Don't worry.
I have a spy among them, sir.
Having a spy will be very
useful for us, Claudius.
But it's not enough.
Tomorrow, all the Lords at the
frontiers will gather in the arena.
We will set the great Byzantine fire.
We will awaken the sleeping
Byzantine spirit once again.
Peace be upon you
Peace be upon you too.
Alaeddin Bey.
Since yesterday, everyone has been
talking about Osman Bey's council.
Do you know the reason for this council?
The Bey speaks at the council, Yigit Bey.
We will all learn together.
Beys...
...the Mongol trouble has
ended, with Allah's help.
Osman Bey will make new
decisions for the people and the state.
The Mongols are gone, but...
...there is disorder in the world, Beys.
I have heard that Turk Beys fight each other.
Germiyan, Karaman.
What will be our place in this war, Beys?
Beys, we are ready for the council.
Osman Bey is waiting for you.
Attention!
Osman Bey!
Peace be upon you
Peace be upon you too.
With Almighty Allah's 99 names..
...Who says "Be", and it is...
...and fills our heart with faith...
...I am opening the council.
In the name of Allah,
the merciful, the compassionate.
We did not...
We did not..
...have many men before.
But we have sent the infidels
away from these borders.
We were a Beylic, now we are a state.
We will restore this state, which the Mongols
have destroyed, to its former strength.
God willing my Bey.
What strengthens a state is justice
and tradition, but treasure is also needed.
The battle with the Mongols
destroyed our treasure, my Bey.
The nomads have no treasure but patched tents.
How will we make this state strong again?
By fighting
War will open the doors to treasure.
The treasure is in the borders
ruled by the oppression of Byzantium.
The nomads fell into war
without settling anywhere.
We fought.
We destroyed the Mongols with Allah's help.
But the Alps are tired, Osman Bey.
We don't have many Alps.
I worry that this battle may bring us defeat.
What do you mean, Hasan
Bey? A sword rusts in its sheath.
An Alp rests in war.
Wait..
Wait...
We are holding a council here.
Here, everyone will say what they wish.
Let the opinions be freed
from the tongue, Koca Bey.
Hasan Bey. Tell us.
The winter has just ended.
The nomads are miserable.
I say let the Alps and
children rejoice with the spring.
Let our horses and sheep
rest in the fields and grow.
Let's gather our strength
and then attack, Osman Bey.
Whenever we wait, the infidels'
swords slit our throat, Hasan Bey.
Waiting always gives courage to the infidel.
Boran Bey is right, but...
What if..
What if we lose?
Then we will be devastated.
The Beylics that want to replace
the Seljuks will have an opportunity.
Therefore, as Hasan Bey said...
...even if it's just precautionary...
...I also think waiting is
the right choice, my Bey.
Courage is needed against the oppressor,
and freedom is needed against slavery, Beys.
Those who are afraid of dying will die!
I say we should not stop but continue, my Bey.
What do you think we should do, Alaeddin?
I am considering...
...the strength of the army
as much as the war, my Bey.
If the army weakens..
...the state's survival will be in danger.
Do you suggest we hold back from war?
-No, never.
But I think it is wise to be cautious, my Bey.
My Beys.
My companions.
I listened to you.
Being a state according
to the Oghuz tradition...
...is only possible with wise Beys like you.
I understand your troubles.
But know this..
As long as we are on the right
path, Allah will always be with us.
God willing, my Bey.
Karesi, Candar, Germiyan, Karaman..
...and all the other Beylics.
All of them..
All of them are trying to be like the Seljuks.
We...
...turn towards conquests...
...instead of turning to their side..
...we will gather many nomads whose hearts...
...burn for war on our lands.
Therefore...
Therefore..
...we will become stronger...
...and our state will become stronger.
All of you have the honor to
serve the great Roman ideal.
You will do the necessary
and protect what is ours.
-Right, Claudius?
-Yes, sir.
While Turks are fighting each
other for the throne left from Seljuks,
...we should reinforce our existence here.
The biggest obstacle against us is Osman.
Instead of fighting Turks and losing power.
...Osman turned to us,
Byzantine, with all his strength.
We need to find out what he plans,
...understand his policy and make use of it.
I agree.
Yet Osman killed Orlok Kucar
and gained great reputation.
The news spread all around.
I agree with Lord Valens.
He will lead all the Turkish Beys who avoid
the race of being the new Seljuk State.
We hear Osman's name too much in Mudurnu.
For this reason exactly.
...we will gather under
the command of our great
emperor and wipe Osman's
name off these lands.
After every trouble, a great reward is offered.
As long as we continue conquering.
...we will make those nomad
settle in the places we conquer.
So we will give the oppressed hope.
Just then we will be the soldiers of
Turks in the plains of Anatolia, Osman Bey.
God willing, my Bey!
-God willing.
God willing, God willing.
Well said, my Bey.
What is our target?
Our target...
..is the northern border.
Here.
Sakarya, Mudurnu, Goynuk.
We will turn to those places.
And we will have raids on them all the time.
All of them are fertile
and watery lands, my Bey.
They will make us stronger.
How will we move our army, my Bey?
Spies of the heathens are
wandering in all the borders.
We will move our army...
...through the hidden valleys in the west.
For this reason,
...everybody should prepare
their alps for these raids.
In two days, we will meet in
Karacam and join together.
As you order, my Bey!
The council is over.
We perform raid, Allah offers victory.
-Aameen!
-Aameen, my Bey!
As you all see,
...the number of his followers is increasing.
His army is growing bigger.
Osman has had an important council today.
He gathered all the Beys.
Claudius and Sofia are supposed to
find out Osman's move after the council...
...and stop him.
And you should tighten the
security measures in your cities.
You should reinforce your armies.
You should organize your people.
In this war, everybody will be a soldier.
-As you wish.
Osman must learn a bitter lesson
that he shouldn't touch what is ours.
The Byzantine fire that we
have raised will burn Osman first.
While migrating, we almost ran out of gold.
With this raid, we will gain some.
It will be a cure for our trouble, God willing.
-God willing.
Fighters practiced with Mongolians.
Now they will hit the Byzantine
borders like thunderbolts!
-My man. -Brother.
Gather the alps.
We will be a sword for the
state and the cure for people.
God willing, brother.
Seyit.
Listen to me carefully.
Hear my words and tell Claudius...
...about them one by one.
Let's talk somewhere safer.
Peace be upon you.
-Peace be upon you too.
I'm ready with my five thousand
war-loving alps, Osman Bey.
For the raid, I'm ready
with my three thousand alps
who have wild horses
running inside, Osman Bey.
Thank you, thank you.
We destroyed the cruel ones one by
one who wanted to invade the Muslim lands.
...we will stick our swords
of justice into their chests.
Our people will share the booties.
We'll always be under the
command of Islam banner.
May The Creator bless our struggle..
-Aameen.
Here we go.
Osman's army will be here soon.
My arches will shoot their arrows on
Osman's army like a storm with my call.
When archers are done, the
infantry will come out of their covers...
...and kill the rest of his army.
Osman, you are going to
die with your army here today.
Why did we stop, my Bey? Did you see something?
Just stop, Koca Bey. Just stop.
What is the news, Kanyumaz?
My Bey, I checked all the
ways in the east as you ordered.
The ways are safe and available
for our army to move through.
There is nobody.
Okay.
In the council, you said
we would ride in the west.
Didn't you, Osman Bey?
Are we changing our route?
Precautions, Koca Bey.
Precautions.
We take precautions, Allah offers victory.
As long as the target is clear,
we can follow every path, my Bey.
Alright. Here we go.
-We'll ride to the east. Let's go.
-Come on.
Let me see.
Sister.
The man you called insane.
-Yes?
-He's been looking here.
Ghazi told me...
-Halime!
Fine.
I didn't say anything.
Why is that insane boy coming here?
Bala Hatun, I want to help
with something if you let me.
You are Koca Bey's son, right?
Yes, my name is Oghuz. I'm at your service.
Thanks, Oghuz.
Stand ready then.
We'll send the carts when we get
the news about Osman Bey's victory.
I'm always ready.
Bala Hatun.
Sofia is here.
She wants to see Halime Hatun.
How dare she come here?
Peace be upon you, Turgut Ghazi.
Peace be upon you too.
They call me Solgur Agha, the lion hunter.
Welcome, Solgur Agha. Alright.
Alright.
We called you and you came instantly. Thank you.
My brothers who would die for
our cause, with Osman Bey's order,
...and I hunt heathens in the frontiers.
I've heard that Osman Bey is having a raid.
You heard right, Solgur Agha.
That's why I gathered you here.
I want to swing the glorious sword
of Turks in the front all together.
We should be an example to young alps.
I don't want them to die.
What do you think history is?
Mad men make history!
We are the maddest!
We only come around in the grave!
We shall die if we have
to die and become martyrs!
We'd gladly die for the Islam world!
For the Islam world!
Praise be, brave fighters.
Praise be.
What are these furs for, Turgut Ghazi?
Our glorious horseshoes always
scared the enemy from the distance.
These furs will make the hearts of
heathens shake with fear, for sure.
God willing.
Long live, Turgut Ghazi.
Thank you.
Let's go join the raid and
slaughter the heathens!
Allah is the greatest!
Allah is the greatest! Allah is the greatest!
Bala.
That we let you live doesn't
mean you can come here freely.
Don't push my patience.
We aren't enemies anymore.
I wanted to see Poena.
My little bird, are you alright?
I'm fine.
You?
I might be better if were with me, though.
How is your disease?
Fine.
You said you were sick and would die.
I asked the healer hatuns
who cured your sickness.
You have no disease, Sofia.
You lied again.
-Poena, I just...
-Wait, mother.
My name is Halime.
And if you come to see me again
...I will kill you with my own hands.
You heard what you needed to hear Sofia.
Go now.
Alps!
Accompany Sofia on the way back.
The carts will set out when
Osman Bey sends word.
Until then, let's do our best, sister.
Right, Bala.
I heard what I needed to hear.
Sir.
Osman will not march to the west,
he will march north with his army.
What do you mean north?
What are you saying?
Why would he turn from his path?
I don't know, sir.
Osman.
Where is his target?
Where will you attack?
Where will this shepherd attack?
Did he tell them?
I only know that they are heading north, sir.
Then, we will go north.
They are far ahead of you, sir.
Even if your horses die, you will not stop.
Osman will not reach his
target, wherever he goes.
Well done, Koca Bey.
Thank you, thank you Alaeddin.
There is no other nation as happy
as us before a war, thanks to Allah.
The battle is a celebration for
the Turks, Shahzade Alaeddin.
Right. Right.
Celebration for us, death for infidels.
You are right!
The sound of your sword
fills my heart with light.
My companion is my sword...
...my way is conquest...
...and my celebration is shahada.
May your life be long, Hasan brother.
Praise be. -Live long.
Thank you Koca Bey.
Thank you.
My Bey is coming.
Peace be upon you.
Peace be upon you too.
We will conquer Goynuk...
...with our swords and rule with justice.
We will keep conquering lands.
And we will take our children's dreams far away
with Beys who see shahada as a celebration.
The time has come.
Now we will strike the infidels like a spear.
God willing
Come! Listen to me!
Walk!
Do not forget!
Come!
Dear Romans!
Do not forget the orders of God!
Get closer to God!
Come here!
Stupid kid.
Forgive me sir.
Take this.
Increase the number of guards.
Claudius will attack Osman's army.
But we still need to be careful.
Father, let's sell these.
No, my daughter. I cannot.
I bought these because you were sick.
You need to eat these to get stronger.
They are here, sir.
By selling these goods at my
market, you are insulting me.
Forgive me, I couldn't work
because my daughter was ill.
Your daughter concerns you.
The marketplace concerns me.
Throw this man out of my marketplace.
Sir, forgive me! My family needs food!
I need to work, otherwise what will they eat?
Forgive me, sir.
Sir, forgive me!
Take him!
Father.
Don't be afraid, my daughter.
Sir, forgive me.
Sir...
Don't be afraid, my daughter.
A small price for the stall.
You can do business in my marketplace.
The stall is now yours.
My little bird..
...is threatening me with death, Hristo.
She is Turk, Sofia.
I raised her!
Like a Christian!
I raised her like my daughter.
And you will send the family
she chose over you to hell.
Claudius..
...will destroy Osman's dream of conquests.
We will also prevent aid
from going from the tribe.
Bala..
...has already prepared carts
full of ammunition and provisions.
Is it clear when the carts will set out?
After Claudius' move, they will ask for help.
We will be near the tribe.
Get ready.
We will raid...
...that caravan.
Come and get some!
Why do you think so?
Lord Valens!
Turks are coming!
Damn it!
Close the doors!
Do not touch their sacred
places, temples and churches!
Inform Claudius!
Attack!
Come on!
Come on
Damn it.
So your target was Goynuk, Osman.
Allah is the Greatest!
Goynuk will be your grave, Osman.
Come. Come here.
Lord Valens... or whatever you are called.
You won't even have a grave.
Your dead body will just decay.
Your time has come.
You can kill me.
But Claudius will not let you get away with it.
You will go to hell with Claudius.
Get rid of his dead body.
Tell me.
Osman... Osman conquered Goynuk, sir.
Damn it.
Are we going back, sir?
No.
We'll wait here.
We will let him think he gained a victory.
I will give him a defeat he will never forget.
Osman.
Don't be scared.
Don't be afraid.
Don t be scared.
Don't be scared.
We brought justice to Goynuk, not death.
Your goods, your lives, your honour...
...are entrusted to me.
Against all kinds of harm....
...my word will be a shield.
Don't... You were not defeated.
Hope and salvation rose like the sun in Goynuk.
Thank you Osman Bey.
Alps, search the houses!
Check if there are soldiers who are hiding!
As you order, my Bey.
Kanyumaz.
Place guards on the walls.
Goynuk is now the property of Kayi.
Let our banner wave on the walls.
Alright brother.
Osman Bey's banner will give fear to
the infidels and hope to the oppressed.
Hay Praise be!
Praise be!
Come on Alps!
In the name of Allah!
Take them where the other prisoners are.
You stop
Let me look at you.
From now on, you will be with me.
Yigit Bey, what are you doing?
Hasan Bey.
I'm taking my share from the booty.
This woman..
...will be my odalisque.
You can't take anything
without Osman Bey's permission.
We need to consult Osman Bey first.
I'm leading a miserable life here.
I'll be happy to be the
odalisque of such a brave Bey.
You heard her.
-Give me patience, my Allah.
-Here we go.
-Alaeddin.
-My Bey.
Are there any Byzantine
soldiers left in the city?
Did you meet the needs of people?
The city is safe, my Bey.
People got fed, for sure.
Thank you.
My Bey, Turgut Ghazi is coming.
Peace be upon you.
Peace be upon you too.
May your conquest be blessed, Osman.
Thank you, Turgut Ghazi.
Thank you.
Well... The elders of my tribe.
Old wolves.
Welcome.
Thank you, Osman Bey.
Praise be, my Bey.
You look very well. Praise be.
Praise be.
Well, Solgur Agha. You carried
out your duty in the frontiers properly.
Now you will stand beside me.
I'd like to fight beside in the front with
Turgut Ghazi with your permission, my Bey.
We will put fear in hearts and
spread the glory of Turks in battlefields.
Surely.
To let the young live longer, we
will sacrifice ourselves, Osman Bey.
Thank you.
Some old men are waiting
for death in their beds.
And some never avoid fights like you.
And this would only suit mad hearts.
Long live everyone.
-Thank you, my Bey.
-Thank you,, my Bey.
We'll gladly sacrifice our lives
for the Islam cause, my Bey.
What is the target?
Tell us so we can leave in no time.
The target
Who is the impertinent man
who comes in without permission?
You betrayed me.
What are you doing here?
You're risking our lives.
I'm here to bring you to account.
Osman didn't use the route that you told me.
I lost Goynuk because of you.
Why would I do that?
Osman tricked all of
He changed the route in the last minute.
I had no time to inform you.
I'm telling the truth.
I lost Goynuk.
I won't lose any other lands.
Don't worry.
Osman will set the new target.
We will catch him this time.
He'll definitely fall into our trap.
You go now.
Don't be caught here.
Wait for my call.
Do not come to me false intelligence again!
Mother.
Yes, my dear?
My father and brothers are having raids.
But we just wait in the tribe.
Will it always be this way?
Well said, sister.
I always complain about this, but...
...nothing changes.
Oh no.
Your job got harder, mother.
You have to deal with two now.
Yes.
A conquest cannot be performed
only with swords, my dear.
How is it performed, mother?
Look at her!
She doesn't say she can't sew but keeps yawning.
Come here. Come closer.
Come. Come here.
My big babies.
Gonca, they both lie on my knees
and say they want to join raids. You see?
-I see.
-Mother.
They have a mother and she spoils them.
Well... Look at me. I can
spoil you too, my pretty girl.
Oh my sister-in-law.
Oh my sister-in-law...
Mother, you said a conquest
cannot be performed only with swords.
How is it performed?
Don't be jealous of my sister at least.
Fatma.
A land is conquered but...
...if a baby isn't born in that
land, you can't own that land.
Mother, we haven't got
any news about father yet.
What do you think they are doing?
Go perform your ablutions. Let's pray. Come on.
Do I have permission Bala Hatun?
Come in, Kismet.
Great news, Bala Hatun.
Kismet, did they?
Osman Bey conquered Goynuk.
Thanks to Allah.
Now we have to take action.
At dawn tomorrow, the
caravan will leave for Goynuk.
Finish the preparations.
-Come on, pack up.
-Alright.
Come on.
We distributed the booties
as you ordered, my Bey.
And we sent their shares
to the houses of our martyrs.
We will give everybody their shares.
Now it's time to encourage
the hearts for the new horizons.
What about the odalisques and
the prisoners we captured, my Bey?
We will inform them about Islam.
Whoever doesn't accept will pay the price.
Those who want to marry our alps can do it.
Those who don't want will be
assigned for duties with our sisters.
As you order, my Bey.
I've built up the fire of battle.
We can't stop now.
They can't stand against the
fate we draw with our swords.
-With Allah's will, my Bey.
When the target is set,
...we will put our iron fists on
the enemy's chest, for sure.
For sure.
Our target is Mudurnu.
The castle of Mudurnu both
stands on the trade route...
...and has very fertile lands, my Bey.
Koca Bey.
Prepare your alps tomorrow morning.
This duty is yours.
As you order, my Bey.
-Alaaddin.
-My Bey.
The catapults and the
battering rams to hit the walls.
This duty is yours.
As you order, my Bey.
Thank you, thank you.
And we will set out at the dawn.
We'll go through the hidden
valleys to reach Mudurnu.
Turgut Ghazi and Solgur
Agha. You will leave tonight.
You need to check all the way.
Alright.
As you order, my Bey.
Here we go. May our fight be blessed.
May Allah let us be
victorious, who follow Islam.
-Aameen.
Aameen.
We placed all the healing materials, mother.
Fine.
Food, clothes, weapons.
We prepared everything, Bala Hatun.
Good. Praise be.
I'll keep watching the tribe with
Sisters and continue the preparations.
-You'll go to Goynuk.
-As you order, mother.
As you order, mother.
Cerkutay Bey, you will watch the carts to make
sure that they reach the army camp safely.
As you order, Bala Hatun.
Oghuz Bey and alps will accompany you.
Have a safe travel.
-Come on.
-Come on, alps!
We have a long way.
Mother, isn't Halime going?
I'm here!
I'm here.
I really have a lot to do with you...
I know you love me, sister.
I love you too.
Come on. Go now.
Come on! Come on.
Attention! Osman Bey!
My Beys. My Alps. We conquered Goynuk.
Now this place belongs to us.
Everyone must know.
Our target is Mudurnu.
They are all waiting for us.
Let them wait for us.
We will bring the justice of Islam
to Rome, where injustice rules.
God willing.
Allah is the Greatest!
Have the soldiers taken their positions?
They are all ready.
They are waiting for your orders.
Good.
Tell them.
Everyone in the caravan will die.
Fatma Hatun.
I am sorry.
What happened?
Are you starting to act smart?
I am asking for your forgiveness.
And you are still calling me a lunatic.
Why are you doing this?
Why are you asking for forgiveness?
I didn't know you were Osman Bey's daughter.
You treat people differently than.
What would you do if I were one of the people?
Would you still ask for forgiveness?
Or are you scared?
I don't know what fear is.
But I made a mistake.
You are seriously arrogant.
And you are a cowardly lunatic.
My Yigit Bey ordered me to give this to you.
Sir.
Tell Yigit Bey...
When this is over, he will be
rewarded for all the things he did.
So you will attack Mudurnu, Osman.
You will pass through narrow passages...
...for the Mudurnu castle.
Those narrow passages will become your grave.
Everyone get ready.
We are leaving.
Archers!
Ambush! Be careful
Be careful!
Behind the carts!
Come on! Come on! Fatma!
Come on.
It's Hristo.
Sofia
I will kill you all!
I will not let this happen!
Stop! Stop, sister.
Now she is our enemy.
Gonca Hatun.
You have the back side.
Attack.
I'll handle it.
Sisters, move to the back!
Alps! Come here! -Attack!
Come on
Sisters!
Every loaf of bread baked
in this oven gives strength
to our valiants who run
from one raid to another.
I know.
You are tired.
But be patient, alright?
Thank you, Bala Hatun.
May Allah bless you, Bala Hatun.
May Allah bless you too.
Bala Hatun!
Kismet!
The watcher Alps saw Byzantine soldiers nearby.
They followed. They are Sofia's soldiers.
Sofia?
Where were they going?
They were close to the road
to Akcatas Cave, Bala Hatun.
She wanted to make peace yesterday.
Sofia..
She will raid the carts..
...going to Goynuk, huh?
Sofia made peace, but...
The snake sheds its skin often...
...but its habit never changes Kismet.
Get ready, we are leaving!
Come on! Come on Kismet!
Come, Osman.
Mudurnu will become your grave.
Get off your horses.
You will burn, Osman!
With this fire, you and those
who believe in you will burn!
You will pay for what you did in Goynuk!
Are you going to scare us with fire, huh?
Alps, attack!
Attack!
Come on, Yigit brother!
Let's kill these infidels!
We will, brother, we will!
Come on valiants!
My Bey! They surrounded us, my Bey!
Hang on!
Come on brothers! Come on!
We melted the iron mountains!
What can they do to us, huh?
Attack!
Sofia!
I told you not to stand before me again.
Calm down, my little bird.
You lied again!
Poena.
This is me, Poena.
But this is not you!
I am suffering in pain
as I see you in this state!
Go to hell, Sofia.
Go to hell.
But I...
...for the first time in my life, I am in peace.
You have one last chance.
You will either come with me...
...or you will die like the rest of your family.
No.
Then you'll watch your sister die, Poena.
Kill Fatma!
No!
I won't let you hurt her!
You still don't understand Sofia.
You cannot scare us with death.
I am behind you, Bey's daughter.
I told you I did not know what fear was.
You were right. Surely, I will
return your favor, Bey's lunatic son.
You go, my Bey!
I will deal with the rest here!
Thank you Turhan!
My Bey, we are stuck here!
It's over Osman! It's over!
I extinguished your fire of conquest!
That was it!
We are here, my Osman!
Allah is the Greatest!
Did you think we did not take precautions?
It's not over until I say it is.
Attack!
You arrived just in time, Turgut Ghazi.
I will be behind you as long as I live, Osman.
Let's kill all the infidels here!
Today we will forget our old age!
Allah is the Greatest!
We are retreating!
Osman, I will come!
I swear I will come for you!
You're running off, huh?
You can run off to the death only!
Go wherever you want.
My Bey.
Thankfully, Turgut Ghazi
and alps came to help in time.
For sure.
But the dog called Claudius...
How did he know about this route?
My Bey.
After Goynuk,
...they must have placed
watchmen all around with fear.
It doesn't matter.
We have only one target.
We'll capture Mudurnu.
Until we capture Mudurnu, our swords
will never go back in their sheathes.
-As you order, my Bey.
As you order, my Bey.
I raised you.
You can't kill me until I want you to do so.
I am...
...the daughter of my mother and father.
Sofia, I'm Kayi.
You can no longer predict my next move.
Halime!
You killed my Poena.
I will kill you.
Halime!
Sofia!
-Mother.
-I will be your death!
Alps, Sisters.
Crush everyone who stands in your way
until Osman Bey's goods reach Goynuk.
Allah is the greatest!
Soldiers, let nobody survive!
Nobody.
I'm Osman Bey.
I have never abandoned the right path.
I have never give up on the cause of Turks.
I have never bowed to anyone
to raise just a little higher.
I've made my father's beylic grow
bigger and develop into a state.
I've stood against the cruel.
I've helped the oppressed.
In this path, death is martyrdom to me.
Now I'm telling my nation...
Either we will fight the pharaohs and vanish...
...or...
...we will rule forever
under the banner of Islam.